[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The discovery of cosmic object 2003 UB313 caused much stir in astronomers circles. Its discoverers declared 2003 UB313 to be what?", "correct_answer": "The tenth planet in the Solar system", "incorrect_answers": ["A new galaxy", "A possible black hole near the edge of the Solar system", "A planetary system with signs of intelligent life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You just need 1 oz white creme de cacao and 1 oz white creme de menthe for this cocktail. They are poured over ice in an old fashioned glass.", "correct_answer": "Peppermint Pattie", "incorrect_answers": ["Kama Sutra", "Kapu-Kai", "Grape Crush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continents does the natural habitat of the jaguar span upon?", "correct_answer": "North and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe and Africa", "South America and Africa", "Africa and Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A chain is a unit of measure used primarily in profession?", "correct_answer": "Surveyor", "incorrect_answers": ["A man in control of letting down the anchor on a ship", "Lumberjacker", "Fence installer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Incredibles, where does the story take place?", "correct_answer": "Metroville", "incorrect_answers": ["Gothicam", "Suburbs of Manhattan", "Mythotica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You should expect this, if fish jump out of the water while the weather is nice.", "correct_answer": "Rain", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainbows", "Extreme heat", "Lightning storm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous baseball pitcher played the role of Skidmark in the movie Kingpin?", "correct_answer": "Roger Clemens", "incorrect_answers": ["Nolan Ryan", "Curt Schilling", "Greg Maddux"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Jomon refers to a historical period in the development of which country?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Brazil", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Thomas J., Vadas best friend in the movie My Girl?", "correct_answer": "Macaulay Culkin", "incorrect_answers": ["Trey Hayden", "Andrew Petton", "Gavin Renolds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many beats per minute does a chickens heart usually beat?", "correct_answer": "280-315", "incorrect_answers": ["100-234", "147-189", "95-124"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie of the Lethal Weapon franchise became the 6th highest-grossing film of 1989?", "correct_answer": "Lethal Weapon 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Lethal Weapon 4", "Lethal Weapon 3", "Lethal Weapon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Walnuts are proven to lower the bad cholesterol due to this chemical compound found in them.", "correct_answer": "Omega-3 fatty acids", "incorrect_answers": ["Capsaicin", "Omega-6 fatty acids", "All of these"]}]